(大蛇丸)サスケ！
Sasuke!
Eye of the Hawk
What is this?
(大蛇丸)何だろう？ これ。
(三代目)おお！ よく見つけたな。
Ah! How lucky of you to find this.
これは 白蛇の脱皮した皮だ。
It's the skin of a white snake.
初めて見た こんなの。
I've never...seen anything
like it before.
ハハッ 実はワシもだよ。
Actually, neither have I.
It's a rare item that
you almost never see.
それは滅多に見ることのできない
珍しいものだぞ。
どうして 白いの？
さあな よくはわかっておらん。
Why is it white?
Well, I don't really know.
そんなこと誰も気にとめんしな。
No one really cares about
such things.
ただ 昔から白蛇は 幸運と
再生の象徴とされとるんだ。
But from times past,
the white snake has been
a symbol of good luck and renewal.
幸運と再生…。
Good luck and renewal...
It must be some sort of karma
for you to find it here.
ここで見つけたのも何かの因縁。
お前の両親も どこかで生まれ
変わっているかもしれんのお。
Perhaps your parents are
now reborn somewhere.
いつかまた
大きくなったお前と会うために。
Maybe someday...
you'll meet them when you're grown up.
それって いつだろう？
さてなあ。
When would that be...?
Who knows? I couldn't say.
それはわからんが。
Nawaki...sure is eager.
《縄樹 気負ってるわね》
≪戦争だからね 今は≫
We're at war...after all.
綱手の小隊が？
Tsunade's team has been...?
(綱手)止まれ！ 止まれ！
止まれ！ 止まれってんだ！
Stop! Stop! Stop!
I said, stop!
That's enough! He's dead!
もうよせ 死んでる。
あ～っ！
《人は何て壊れやすいものなの》
Humans...are such fragile beings.
《人体には 一生のうちに➡
Power that was not used in a lifetime
rests inside the human body.
使われることのない力が
眠っている。
If we could release that power...
その力を解放できれば…！》
Orochimaru Sensei!
(アンコ)大蛇丸先生！
これ何です？
What is this?
An amulet.
お守りよ。
お守り？ これが!?
An amulet...? This...?
フフッ それはね
とっても珍しい➡
It's a very rare amulet for
good luck and renewal.
再生と幸運のお守りなのよ。
再生？ これで？
Renewal? With this...?
でも いくら大蛇丸先生が
研究熱心だとしても➡
But...Orochimaru Sensei,
no matter how earnest you are
about your research,
you can't bring back the dead,
can you?
死んじゃった人は
生き返らないですよね？
そうね。
死者の復活は難しいわね。
Yes... Bringing the dead
back to life is difficult.
でもね 再生のヒントなら
掴んでるの！
But, I've grasped a clue
about regeneration.
肉体を活性化させることで
人は格段に強くなり➡
By activating their bodies,
humans can become immensely
more powerful
それと同時に
再生力も高まるのよ。
and heighten their regenerative powers too.
あなたにもいずれ
その力を分けてあげるわね。
I will share that power
with you some day, as well.
Yes! Thank you very much,
Orochimaru Sensei!
はい！ ありがとうございます！
大蛇丸先生！
《呪印という名の
肉体活性術をね》
The Body Activating Jutsu
called the Curse Mark...
How foolish!
There's a limit to unreasonable training!
《大蛇丸 : バカな！
ムチャな修業にもほどがある！》
Beautiful...
美しい… これが写輪眼の力！
So this is the power of the Sharingan.
どれほどの忍が この領域に…。
No matter how many Ninja try
to enter this territory...
どれほどの修業をしようと➡
No matter how hard they train,
they could never surpass the Uchiha.
うちはの血を
超えることなんて…。
ENTRY RESTRICTED
TRANSFER
《わかる…。
I understand...
私には
この術式のすごさがわかる…。
I understand the awesomeness
of this Jutsu...
でも この禁術を会得するのには
最低 １か月…》
TRANSFER
But, it would take at least one month
to master this Forbidden Jutsu...
《ここにある術を
すべて会得するのに➡
How many years would it take
to master all the Jutsu that are here...?
いったい何年かかるというの!?
人の持つ
限られた時間のなかでは➡
It's impossible to grasp all the Jutsu
within the limited time
of a human lifespan...
すべての術を
手にすることは不可能。
There would be a limit
even if I could extend my life
たとえ 再生忍術で
生き長らえたとしても➡
via a Reanimation Jutsu...
それは有限。
死ねば すべては失われてしまう》
Once I die, everything would be lost...
In order to grasp every Jutsu,
I would have to...
《すべてを手に入れるには…》
大蛇丸。 やはり キサマか。
Orochimaru! So it was you,
just as I suspected...
言え。 ここで何をやっていた？
Tell me! What were you doing here?
フフフフ… あなたには
理解できないでしょうね。
You probably couldn't understand...
自らの理よりも
里を優先する あなたには。
You who puts the village
before your own reason.
(大蛇丸)私にとって
肉体の寿命は短すぎる。
To me, the lifespan of
the human body is too short.
たとえ 火影と呼ばれようとも➡
Even if I were to be called a Hokage,
死ねば すべては
そこで終わりですから。
once I die,
everything would end there.
まさか… ここで
実験している術は…。
The Jutsu you're experimenting with...
It can't be...?!
その まさか…
不老不死の術ですよ。
That very one...
the Immortality Jutsu!
(自来也)もう考え直しては
くれないのか？ 大蛇丸。
Can't you reconsider Orochimaru?
笑止！
Out of the question!
バカにも程がある。
How stupid can you be?!
I'm so close...
《あと一歩…。
So close with my research.
あと一歩のところまで
研究は進んでいる》
《私は すべてを手に入れる。
I will have everything.
私の器は
この体でも木ノ葉でもない。
My vessel is neither this body,
nor the Leaf!
そのためには 組織だろうと
何だろうと利用するまで！》
To that end, I will use that organization
and anything else!
新しいメンバーの到着だ。
A new member has arrived.
うちはイタチ…。
Itachi Uchiha.
《うちはを滅ぼしたあなたが
暁に来るなんてね…》
You destroyed the Uchiha.
What brings you to the Akatsuki?
貴重な写輪眼を持つ者が
自ら私の前に…。
One who possesses the precious Sharingan
appears before me...
なんてラッキーなのかしら 私は。
How lucky I am...
さあ その体 いただくわよ！
I will have your body!
うっ…。
まさか… この私が
金縛りの幻術に…。
Could it be...that I...
am under a Paralysis Genjutsu...
What visual prowess...
なんという瞳力… すばらしい!!
Marvelous...
うっ…。
Orochimaru...
(イタチ)大蛇丸
お前のいかなる術も➡
Any Jutsu you use will have
no effect before these eyes.
この眼の前では
なんの効力も持たない。
フフフフッ… 来たわね。
You've come.
(さあ 行きましょう))
Now, let's go...
《私の未来は この子の中にある》
My future lies in this child!
It's over... That was too quick.
(サスケ)終わりか…
あまりにもあっけない。
うっ… うぅ…。
フフフフ… そろそろ
効いてきたみたいね。
Looks like it's beginning
to take effect...
この大白蛇の体液は➡
The body fluid of the giant white snake skin
vaporizes upon contact with the air
空気に触れると気化する
痺れ薬なのよ。
and becomes an anesthetic.
私は 不滅。
I am immortal.
あなたごときの術では
まだまだ殺せぬ。
The likes of your Jutsu cannot kill me...!
Now then...
さあ！ いただくわよ！
I shall have you now!
何だ？
What is this?
This is...a different space inside my body.
(大蛇丸)ここは
私の中にある異空間。
Here, the Transference Ritual will be held...
ここで転生の儀式を行うのよ。
We'll begin now.
始めるわ。
What visual prowess... Marvelous...
《大蛇丸 : なんという瞳力…。
すばらしい。
これは まるで あのときの！》
This is almost like...that time...
フフフフフ… ハハハハハ！
その眼… その眼が
ついに私のものに！
Those eyes...
Those eyes will be mine at last...!
《カブト : 薬じゃ もうもたないな…。
He won't last with only the medicine...
He'll have to do the Transference Ritual
as soon as today...
早ければ今日にも転生の儀式を
行うしかないか…》
《しかし あのサスケ君が
素直に うんと言うとは思えない》
But...
It's hard to believe that
Sasuke would consent willingly...
《フン まあ サスケ君といえども
あの儀式には逆らえまいが》
Well, even Sasuke can't resist that ritual...
Why is Sasuke here?!
《どうして サスケ君がここに…。
あれは 巨大ヘビの脱皮。
That is the cast-off skin
of the giant snake...
ということは
すでに 儀式が終わったのか》
Does that mean the ritual
is already done?
《いったい どうなってる？》
What's going on?
カブトか？
Kabuto, is that you?
今のキミは
いったい どっちなんです？
Which one...
are you now?
どっちだと思う？
Which one do you think?
《これは転生の儀式。
This is the Transference Ritual!
転生の儀式の記憶を
見せられているんだ。
He's showing me the memories
of the Transference Ritual!
The ritual between the two
will be settled right now!
これから ２人の儀式に
決着がつく》
((これは…。
What the--?!
(大蛇丸)バカな ここは
私の作り出した異空間よ。
ありえない ありえない！
ありえないわ。
ここは私だけの…。
大蛇丸。
お前のいかなる術も
この眼の前では…。
(もう わかってるはずだろう？))
《なんて おぞましい。
サスケ君の意思が
空間を侵食していく》
((大蛇丸 : ああ こんな…
こんなことがあってたまるか！
私は 不死の大蛇丸だぞ！
こんな こんなところで！
こんなところで この私が!!
私は この世を解き明かす者。
(すべてを 手にする者なのだ…))
(ナルト)
なんか イヤな雲行きだってばよ。
まるで…。
(自来也)燃ゆる落日。
血のようじゃな。
(鬼鮫)どうしました？
いや なんでもない。
大蛇丸様が 死んだ…。
いや これではまるで…。
オレが ヤツのすべてを
のっとったのさ。
(ルーシィ)あぁ 気持いい。
やっぱり 自分家は 落ち着くな。
(カナ)いいとこね。
でしょ！ ん？
私も ここに住もうかな。
ギャ～ッ！